{
    "question": "Thankyou momy you for risking your life your useless doughter this love",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p> Terima kasih ibu, kau telah mempertaruhkan nyawamu demi cintamu yang tak berguna ini</p><p></p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "4-read-this-song-carefully-ben-by-michael-jackson-ben-the-tw-146",
            "question": "4. read this song carefully! \"ben\" by michael jackson ben, the two of us need look no more we both find what we were looking for with a friend to call my own i'll never be alone and you my friend will see you've got a friend in me ben, you're always running here and there you feel you're not wanted anywhere if you ever look behind and don't like what you find there's one thing you should know you've got a place to go a. the song is about .... b. \"there's one thing you should know. you've got a place to go\" the lyrics means ... c. through the song, the singer wants the listener to know about\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. Friend</p><p>2. You can go to your friend when yo don&#039;t know where to go</p><p>3. You&#039;ve got a friend that will always be with you</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "you-have-asking-your-family-member-about-their-habit-533",
            "question": "You have asking your family member about their habit\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>kamu telah menanyakan ke keluargamu tentang hobi mereka</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "kotak-amal-di-masjid-al-aqsa-menyerupai-kubus-jika-masing-masing-817",
            "question": "kotak amal di masjid al aqsa menyerupai kubus, jika masing-masing kotak amal memiliki panjang rusuk 5cm maka volume ketiga kotak amal adalah...cm\u00b3\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>v1 = s\u00b3= s\u00d7s\u00d7s</p><p>   = 5\u00d75\u00d75</p><p>   =125cm\u00b3</p><p></p><p>v2= s\u00b3= s\u00d7s\u00d7s</p><p>   = 5\u00d75\u00d75</p><p>   =125cm\u00b3</p><p></p><p>v3 = s\u00b3= s\u00d7s\u00d7s</p><p>   = 5\u00d75\u00d75</p><p>   =125cm\u00b3</p><p></p><p>v1+v2+v3 = 125+125+125</p><p>                 = 375cm\u00b3</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>maaf kalau salah</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "d-dream-23-what-does-the-song-tell-us-about-a-love-b-friendsh-911",
            "question": "D. Dream\r\n23. What does the song tell us about?\r\nA Love\r\nB. Friendship\r\nc. Family\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>mohon maaf tapi songnya(lagu) mana yah? judulnya apa? kalo judul nya \"you got a friend\"</p><p>jawaban lebih baik pilih B. friendship</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "this-song-is-for-question-no-42-44-flashlight-jessie-j-when-tom-287",
            "question": "This song is for question no. 42-44!    Flashlight\r\nJessie J\r\nWhen tomorrow comes\r\nI'll be on my own\r\nFeeling frightened of\r\nThe things that I don't know\r\nWhen tomorrow comes Tomorrow comes\r\nTomorrow comes\r\nAnd though the road is long\r\nI look up to the sky\r\nAnd in the dark I found,\r\nI lost hope that I won't fly\r\nAnd I sing along, I sing along\r\nAnd I sing along\r\nI got all I need when I got you and I\r\nI look around me, and see a sweet life\r\nI'm stuck in the dark but you're my\r\nflashlight\r\nYou're getting me, getting me\r\nthrough the night\r\nKick start my heart when you shine it in\r\nmy eyes\r\nCan't lie, it's a sweet life\r\nI'm stuck in the dark but\r\nyou're my flashlight\r\nYou're getting me, getting me\r\nthrough the night\r\n'Cause you're my flashlight (flashlight)\r\nYou're my flashlight (flashlight)\r\nYou're my flash\r\n42. What is the song about?\r\nA. The singer's new flashlight.\r\nB. The singer's day after tomorrow.\r\nC. The singer's dark side.\r\nD. The singer's special one.\r\n43. How does the writer feel about tomorrow?\r\nA. Happy\r\nB. Sad\r\nC. Scared\r\nD. Stuck\r\n44. Why does the singer sing this song?\r\nA. To show her feeling about tomorrow\r\nB. To help people overcome their problem\r\nC To ask for help because she is always frightened\r\nD. To express her gratitude to have that someone by her side\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>42. D. The singer&#039;s special one</p><p>43. C. Scared</p><p>44. D. To express her gratitude to have someone by her side.</p><p></p><p>Penjelasan: </p><p>hope this find you helpful ^\u2022^ </p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "siapa-saja-yang-termasuk-al-khulafa-u-ar-yasidin-sebutkan-650",
            "question": "Siapa saja yang termasuk al khulafa u ar yasidin sebutkan\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Abu Bakar Ash-Shiddiq,Umar bin Khattab,Utsman bin Affan,Ali bin Abi Thalib</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "edo-is-swimming-in-the-river-he-wears-411",
            "question": "Edo is swimming in the river. he wears\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p><strong>Swimsuit or wetsuit</strong></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Maaf kalau salah, semoga membantu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>swimming goggles and swimsuit</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>sorry if it&#039;s wrong help follow and make the best answer</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "fill-in-the-blanks-with-tobe-am-is-are-for-example-my-moth-393",
            "question": "Fill in the blanks with tobe (am/ is/ are).    For example : My mother ... beautiful.\r\n My mother is beautiful.\r\n (She)\r\n1.My friends ... in the library.\r\n\r\n2.I and my brothers ... at our uncle home.\r\n\r\n3.My sisters ... diligent and smart.\r\n\r\n4.My aunts ... kind and beuatiful.\r\n\r\n5.The tiger ... wild.\r\n\r\n6.The sharpener ... sharp.\r\n\r\n7.Anton and Andi ... in the field.\r\n\r\n8.My niece ... still baby.\r\n\r\n9.The teachers ... in the classroom.\r\n\r\n10.My grandmother and my grandfather ... at our home.\r\n\r\npliss dijawab\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. is</p><p>2. are</p><p>3. is</p><p>4. is</p><p>5. is</p><p>6. is</p><p>7. are</p><p>8. is</p><p>9. are</p><p>10. are</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "were-the-chlldren-playing-volly-ball-at-10-oclok-in-the-morning-836",
            "question": "Were the chlldren playing volly ball at 10 o'clok in the morning is from asentece from apa jwb ini",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Apakah anak-anak bermain bola volly pada jam 10 pagi adalah dari asentece dari</p><p>(maaf kalo salh</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "analyze-the-texts-below-to-answer-the-question-number-6-text-b-t-801",
            "question": "Analyze the texts below to answer the question number 6!    Text B\r\nText A\r\nI only slept for three hours last night At ten, we heard Last Saturday, my little sister, Dina, did something\r\na cry from Mrs. Wayan's home. She is our next-door funny. She got up very late, at six. She ran fast to the\r\nneighbour She's 70 years old and very weak. She lives bathroom. She thought she would be late to school\r\n. She\r\nalone We went there quickly, and we found her on the forgot it was Saturday. She took a very quick bath, got\r\nfloor\r\n. She just fell She could not move her hands and dressed, took her bag, and ran off to school. She did not\r\nher legs. At 10.30, my parents and I took Mrs. Wayan even have breakfast. After walking for five minutes, she\r\nto hospital. My father and I sat in the front seats. In the noticed that no other children were going to school\r\nback seats, my mum was holding Mrs. Wayan. In the Soon she realized it was Saturday! So, she walked back\r\nemergency room, a doctor examined her. Then, he said\r\nhome. We all laughed at her when she got home. She\r\nMrs. Wayan had to stay in the hospital. When she was also laughed at herself. Then she changed her clothes\r\nalready in the ward, we went home. It was 2 am. and went back to bed! My naughty sister!\r\n sebutkan kata benda dari dua teks tersebut. minimal 3\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>hands, bag, seats, clothes, legs</p><p>Penjelasan:</p><p>smga membantu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>bag,bed,dress</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}